DEMI HAYASHI

FULL-STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Q Los Angeles, CA

hayashi.demi@gmail.com



561-713-5699



github.com/demivlkv



demihayashi.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Motivated full-stack web developer dedicated to writing efficient, high-performance code that prioritizes user experience and accessibility. Self-sufficient quick learner and inspired team-player with extensive experience in prioritizing the clients' needs and working effectively in both team and independent settings, with a background in the service industry.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER @ NEXALURE TECHNOLOGIES (Jan 2024 - Present)

- » Drive the development of efficient and maintainable code, leveraging expertise in React, TypeScript, Redux, NextJS, Node, MongoDB, and SCSS within a meticulously crafted component-based architecture tailored for contemporary web browsers
- » Demonstrate proficiency in troubleshooting, debugging, and optimizing existing software applications by executing rigorous testing protocols to identify and resolve bugs and performance issues
- » Collaborate within a team of 10 in Agile environment and provided help to other team members when needed; handled version control and resolved merge conflicts in Git
- » Proactively participate in collaborative code reviews, cultivating a culture of excellence in code quality and knowledge sharing; actively contributed in stand-ups, estimations, sprint planning, and retrospectives

FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER @ TOKIO RAMEN (Mar 2020 - Jan 2024)

- >> Revamped website of a local ramen shop business to create a fresh, front-end web app
- » Cultivated positive and enduring relationships with clients, and demonstrated bilingual skills to serve English-speaking and Japanese-speaking clients
- >> Focused on application's performance by utilizing GatsbyJS. Other technologies used include GraphQL, JavaScript, and Tailwind CSS

PROJECTS

TRIP TIDE (December 2022 - March 2023)

- >> Created a travel-themed full-stack web application serving as a comprehensive resource for travel-related information and discussion for travel enthusiasts
- >> Implemented client-side using React and Tailwind CSS, and connected server-side APIs, MongoDB, & GraphQL to handle user interactivity, protection of sensitive user information, and data manipulation

BOOK NOOK (September 2022)

- >> Participated in a collaboration with five developers to construct a MERN-stack web application, where users can discuss books, search books, and get book recommendations from other users
- » Designed multiple UI wireframes and layouts to effectively appeal to the target audience

SKILLS

LANGUAGES

» JavaScript (ES6+), TypeScript, CSS3, HTML5

TECHNOLOGIES

» React.js, Next.js, Node.js, Express.js, Redux, RESTful APIs, GraphQL, Contentful CMS, Webpack, jQuery, Sass/SCSS, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS. Materialize

DATABASES

>> MySQL, MongoDB

TOOLS

» Git, GitHub, Heroku, npm, Adobe Photoshop

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF CENTRAL FLORIDA

(June 2022 - November 2022)

- >> Coding Bootcamp
- » Certificate of Completion

UNIVERSITY OF FLORIDA

(Fall 2009 - Spring 2013)

- » Bachelor of Fine Arts
- » Concentration in Creative Photography
- » Graduated Cum Laude

FOREIGN LANGUAGES

JAPANESE

» Native proficiency